Contact

juliemak@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/julie-makatura-4816b977 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

BLS

Acute Care

Certifications

Medical Surgical ANCC

Certified Professional of Healthcare Quality

Certified Lacatation Educator Inpatient Obstetrics

Julie Makatura

MSN, RNC-OB, CPHQ, Senior Quality Nurse at Denver Health Denver

Summary

Experienced Senior Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Medical-Surgical, Obstetrics, Pediatrics, Telemetry, and Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS). Strong quality assurance professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration from Fort Hays State University.

Experience

Denver Health

15 years 2 months

Senior Quality Nurse

February 2011 - Present (9 years 7 months)

Quality initiatives including performance improvement, error reduction and improving patient outcomes

Registered Nurse

July 2005 - February 2011 (5 years 8 months)

Charge Nurse on Mom Baby Unit

University of New Mexico

Registered Nurse

November 1994 - June 2005 (10 years 8 months)

Charge Nurse on High Risk Maternal Child Unit and Charge Nurse on Cardio-Thoracic Step Down Unit (Progressive Care)

Rapid City Regional Hospital

Registered Nurse

May 1993 - October 1994 (1 year 6 months)

Staff nurse on a Medical Surgical Telemetry Unit and also worked on a short stay observation unit for surgical patients

United States Air Force
Missile Systems Maintenance Analyst

Page 1 of 2

December 1986 - September 1992 (5 years 10 months) Ellsworth AFB, SD

Quality Assurance and Missile System Maintenance

Education

Fort Hays State University

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2013 - 2016)

The University of New Mexico
Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science · (1998 - 2000)

The University of South Dakota Associate's degree, Nursing Science · (1991 - 1993)